freesteamkeys.com 2019-06-06

# Privacy Policy | FREE STEAM KEYS

**GENERAL**

Your privacy is important to us. Our Privacy Policy describes our practices concerning data that you provide or that we may collect about you through the Services, and you consent to our use of data in compliance with the Privacy Policy.

 **COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

FreeSteamKeys.com does not sell, exchange, or release your personal information without your consent to any third parties.

 **USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We use Personal Information for our own internal purposes including contacting you via email to inform you about updates to Site. We reserve the right to disclose your information as required by law. We do not rent or sell our Users’ Personal Information to third parties. We do, however, provide you with the opportunity to receive newsletters via email. If you decide to opt in to receive newsletters, you may opt out of receiving these newsletters at any time. We use your IP address and browser information to help diagnose problems with our server and to gather broad demographic information.

Sweepstakes, giveaways, [contests](https://www.freesteamkeys.com/contests/), and promotions on the Services may also have additional rules and eligibility requirements, such as certain age or geographic area restrictions, and you are responsible for complying with these rules and requirements.

 **COOKIES**

Cookies are small data files that a website you visit may save on your computer or handheld device that usually includes an anonymous unique identifier. Our Website may use cookies for user authentication, tracking our audience size and traffic patterns.

Information gathered through the use of cookies is not related to any personally identifiable details. Many browsers are set to accept cookies. You may prefer to set your browser to refuse cookies. It is possible, however, that some areas of the site will not function properly if you do so.

 **THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES**

Third-party advertisers, links, websites and third-party apps (like Rafflecopter, Gleam, and others) may ask your email, or other information, and also create and access cookies, which will be subject to their privacy policies – we accept no responsibility or liability for the use of such third parties’ websites.

If you access a third party website from the Site, Applications or Service, you do so at your own risk, and you understand that this Agreement and our Privacy Policy do not apply to your use of such sites.

 **POLICY CHANGES**

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice. You are advised to check our Website regularly to view our most recent privacy policy.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy please email our team at contact@freesteamkeys.com
